Music
Thank you for watching
First question.
What is your name?
Jun Muto.
How did you come up with your name?
Well, I guess it's the number of strokes in the kanji.
I heard that 15 strokes are very good,
It is said to be able to fill in all kinds of gaps,
It is said to be able to moisten and fill in various gaps.
What is it called?
I guess they call me in order.
Where are you from?
Tokyo.
What is your birthday?
August 18, 2001.
What is your blood type?
AB.
Which part of your face do you like best?
Yes, my mouth.
My mouth.
What are your hobbies?
Gunpla.
I also like watching movies.
I value watching movies at the cinema very much.
I watch about 4 movies at the cinema.
What are your special skills?
Well, I did karate for 10 years,
I can do dance performance.
There is the oldest performance in the world, and I earned a black belt in it.
Do you do anything interesting?
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
That?
Oh, man.
I dropped my courage somewhere.
Next time preview
Next trailer
next preview
preview of the next show
Sticker for the first show
Sticker
Old memories
I cried when I was born
Motivation please
It hurts.
Are you kind?
Is it Ryota Nagano?
Maybe he doesn't even know he's doing it.
He's doing the kindest thing he can.
Is he strict?
Yoshida doesn't ask me to be.
He's become more strict since he became leader.
It's a good thing.
But I think Tankard is very stoic.
They do muscle training during breaks.
In front of everyone...
I think he looks cute in front of everyone.
But on the inside, he's stoic.
A poker face?
No. Masaya Sakuragi, I think.
He's so smart.
He's saying amazing things to his grandchildren.
He's reciting mathematical formulas.
Like, "I've perfected this equation.
But what do you think about it?
What do you think you are in real life?
Ali.
I don't know any of the members anymore.
I don't know.
I often remind myself not to step on the heels of shoes.
I step on my own heels the most.
Is this the one thing you can't lose to anyone else?
Love of reality
Is there someone you'd like to meet?
Can Ami Zeami, I guess.
My boom?
Honey.
Manuka honey.
It's good for the throat.
I'm looking for the best honey for me.
How do I spend my day?
I go to the cinema and watch a movie.
I try to be in the middle of the movie theater.
I want to see my next movie in the same theater.
I leave and get the exact same seat again.
That's right.
Some days, I'm in this seat half the day.
What kind of kid were you?
I watched a lot of cartoons and stuff with my dad.
I thought I was a fighter.
He told me to learn a little bit about what it means to fight.
So I joined karate, and I got beat up a lot.
I was a kid who was learning that fighting is to protect what's important.
That's what I learned when I was a kid.
I love "Chocolate Planet" and others.
If the earth were to die tomorrow, what would you do?
I'd like to be watching a movie and find out that I'd be wiped out by sweat.
There's a bird called a loon that never moves.
Don't think about anything for a long time.
Like this.
It's like a stone statue of a creature.
Hashibiroko
If you were to write one kanji character, what would it be?
I think it's "pure.
Moist
Where would you like to travel?
I would like to travel to Germany.
The food looks delicious and they have a strong soccer team.
Do you easily forget about bad things, or do they linger?
I think that the most unpleasant things drag on for a long time.
But I think I'll use it as food for thought on how to avoid such things from happening.
I don't forget them in order to try to move forward.
Difficult Enemies
Difficult enemy
Difficult Enemy
Here
here
Here are some questions from our observers
What is your favorite outfit?
I think it's the outfit I wore the other day when I was in Pialina's MM.
What is your favorite onigiri ingredient?
Tuna mayo
What do you value most?
Being able to support others.
What is your favorite phrase in your part?
Cherry blossom ground
The most important treasure was there
What was your favorite sport at the gymnastics festival?
Proportional selection of all elementary, junior high and high school athletes.
I was the fastest.
But in my last athletic meet as a junior high school student.
I fell down hard.
When I got back to my class.
I found a lot of bansaucon in my desk.
I cried.
"You're all good guys," he said.
What's a reward for being a good guy?
Keep up the good work.
Good luck.
What is your favorite choreographed local song?
What's the most fun to do?
Pomegranate
The chorus of the song "Pomegranate
Like this...
Poof!
It's called "poof".
They gradually form a horizontal line and pretend to move forward.
The passion of the seven of them... their presence...
I really like it.
What do you want to eat now?
Ramen noodles.
If you had 7 days off, what would you do?
Gunpla.
If you were a family of seven, what would your family consist of?
Taka and his mother, Masaya is the older brother, and Kosaku is the older brother.
Masaya is the oldest, Kosaku is the next, and Ryota is Kosaku's younger brother.
I'm the youngest, and you're the oldest. Kaname, your father.
Where do you want to sit in the classroom?
The very back, one in front of the window.
Do you want to explore reality, Ai?
What do you mean?
What do you mean by "Genki"?
Uh-oh.
Ehh...
Ji
Tama-ta
Ehh...
Boo
It is a lie
No, it's not.
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Odenobu
Matsugi-kun...
Let's see...
KINCHAKU
Takato is
hanpen
I am
daikon
and it's a shirataki.
If it's a kazu, it's probably shirataki
konnyaku kaname
Who do you think it is now?
Oh, I'm sorry, it's just...
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
I'm sorry, but honestly...
It's like a question about how much oden I can say.
What was it?
Uh...
That's what it is, you know.
Beef tendon?
Uh...
Wiener.
Well, well, well.
Vienna sausage
Mm-hmm.
If you could change from your side, what color would it be?
Gray.
What was your favorite picture book?
Jack and My Meloki
What do you think makes the proto-linguistic language so appealing?
Artistic
Which song do you enjoy singing in proto-linguistic?
Choco Loop
Please describe your favorite emoji with your face.
I don't use emoji.
What's for breakfast today?
A loaf of bread and three croissants.
What is the most relaxing or restful time of the day?
Gunpla
What do you need for rehearsals? Food and things
Well, I don't eat much during rehearsals.
But I do need bread.
If you weren't acting or playing music, what would you be?
I was making Gunpla.
Who has inspired you recently?
Cars and...
No load.
Articles in magazines...
I like it.
I think it's really cool.
If you were an animal, what would you do?
A turtle.
If you could switch places for a day, who would you be?
Hmmm... and...
Ozanobudana
What is the name of your show in a country other than Japan?
Mongolia
I've heard and seen a lot of Mongolia in Japan.
So in a little while, they'll be over there too.
I think they might be interested in our country's entertainment.
Who do you respect?
I guess Oda's village.
I remember watching that.
Godzilla-1
I liked the visuals and Ryunosuke Kamiki's performance.
Ryunosuke Kamiki's acting was great.
And I thought it had a lot of the goodness of Godzilla's work in it.
I thought it was pretty good.
What do you look for when choosing clothes?
I tend to choose white, black, or monotone colors.
And in the winter...
As long as it's warm.
What kind of bread do you buy at the bakery?
Anpan (sweet bean paste buns)
What appeals to you?
I feel like an autogor.
Please tell us three good things that happened this week.
I think it was reading the latest issue.
Um, of the manga.
Also, there is an anime where you can't watch the last episode.
Once I saw the last episode, I thought, "Oh, it's over.
I finally watched the one I had been filming for a long time.
I was glad that I finally saw it.
And I made my own pasta, and it was delicious!
What gives you energy?
Hmmm...
I guess it's all my online.
What is your favorite side dish?
Let's see...
Spinach.
I love it.
What do you think of yourself?
Foxy grapes, I guess.
And you?
Yes, sir.
Plankton.
What's the last dance of your life?
Oh, my God.
White rice. Rice.
No more cut-guns?
No. I'm sorry.
What's your favorite seat on the bullet train?
The window seat, I guess.
Where do you want to go now?
Uh, Germany.
What's the latest foreign word you learned?
Jutre. It's French.
It means "I want you.
I'll be right with you.
Well, if it makes you sleepy...
Then show me your favorite recent photo.
There was a show at the Arena.
The one taken right after that?
Yes.
The building itself was new.
I thought it was beautiful.
And the dressing room.
When do you feel happy in winter?
When I'm warm, I guess.
The moment you come out of the cold and into the house.
That's when I feel happy.
What four-letter idiom comes to mind?
Electro-acoustic fire
What sport are you good at?
Basketball
What is the most impressive dream you had while sleeping?
It was a stage rehearsal.
I was sleeping while doing a simulation.
I got a little excited
I was in a scene where I had to give an ogre
I woke up like this.
I thought I was dreaming and went back to sleep.
What were your dreams when you were little?
I don't know.
I liked being a car designer.
That's why I thought maybe I'd like to go to Germany.
Coffee drinker or tea drinker? Tea drinker?
I used to be a tea drinker, but now I'm a coffee drinker.
Favorite doughnut?
Conderelling.
Favorite food?
Miso soup.
What would you like to try most right now?
I want to drive a motorcycle.
What song would you like people to listen to the most?
After all, the cause is me.
Debut song
What is your goal for this year?
This year, I want to finish as many Gunpla I have at home that I haven't made yet.
I want to finish as many as possible.
Any last words?
Well, I'm still in the middle of it.
I'm the oldest person in the world, and I'm the cause of it.
I will do my best on YouTube!
I hope you enjoy it!
Thank you very much.